Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
- West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.10 (1952: May 16)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.11 (1952: May 30)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.12 (1952: June 13)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.13 (1952: June 27)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (1952: July 11)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.2 (1952: July 28)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.3 (1952: Aug. 8)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.4 (1952: Aug. 22)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.5 (1952: Sept. 5)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.6 (1952: Sept. 19)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.7 (1952: Oct. 3)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.8 (1952: Oct. 17)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.9 (1952: Oct. 31)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.10 (1952: Nov. 14)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.12 (1952: Dec. 12)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1952; Publication (Box 141, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.13 (1952: Dec. 26)
- West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1953: Jan. 9)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (1953: Jan. 23)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.3 (1953: Feb. 6)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.5 (1953: Mar. 6)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.6 (1953: Mar. 20)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.7 (1953: Apr. 3)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.8 (1953: Apr. 17)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.9 (1953: May 1)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.10 (1953: May 15)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.11 (1953: May 29)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.12 (1953: June 12)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.13 (1953: June 26)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.14 (1953: July 10)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.15 (1953: July 24)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.16 (1953: Aug. 7)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.17 (1953: Aug. 21)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.18 (1953: Sept. 4)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.19 (1953: Sept. 18)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.20 (1953: Oct. 2)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.21 (1953: Oct. 16)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.22 (1953: Oct. 30)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.23 (1953: Nov. 13)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.24 (1953: Nov. 27)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1953; Publication (Box 141, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.25 (1953: Dec. 11)
- West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1954: Jan. 8)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1954: Jan. 22)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1954: Feb. 5)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1954: Feb. 19)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.5 (1954: Mar. 5)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.6 (1954: Mar. 19)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.7 (1954: Apr. 2)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.12 (1954: Apr. 16)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.13 (1954: Apr. 30)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.14 (1954: May 14)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.15 (1954: May 28)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.16 (1954: June 11)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.17 (1954: June 25)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.18 (1954: July 9)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.19 (1954: July 23)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.20 (1954: Aug. 6)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.21 (1954: Aug. 20)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.22 (1954: Sept. 3)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.23 (1954: Sept. 17)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.24 (1954: Oct. 1)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.25 (1954: Oct. 15)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.26 (1954: Oct. 29)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.27 (1954: Nov. 12)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.28 (1954: Nov. 26)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.29 (1954: Dec. 10)
  - Item 26: West Coast Sailors, 1954; Publication (Box 141, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.30 (1954: Dec. 24)
- West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1955: Jan. 7)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.2 (1955: Jan. 21)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.3 (1955: Feb. 4)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.4 (1955: Feb. 18)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.5 (1955: Mar. 4)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.6 (1955: Mar. 18)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.7 (1955: Apr. 1)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.8 (1955: Apr. 15)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.10 (1955: May 13)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.11 (1955: May 27)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.12 (1955: June 10)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.13 (1955: June 24)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.14 (1955: July 8)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.15 (1955: July 22)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.16 (1955: Aug. 5)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.17 (1955: Aug. 19)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.18 (1955: Sept. 2)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.19 (1955: Sept. 16)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.20 (1955: Sept. 30)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.21 (1955: Oct. 14)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.22 (1955: Oct. 28)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.23 (1955: Nov. 11)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.24 (1955: Nov. 25)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.25 (1955: Dec. 9)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1955; Publication (Box 141, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.26 (1955: Dec. 23)
- West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.1 (1956: Jan. 6)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.2 (1956: Jan. 20)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.3 (1956: Feb. 3)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.4 (1956: Feb. 17)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.5 (1956: Mar. 2)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.6 (1956: Mar. 16)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.7 (1956: Mar. 30)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.8 (1956: Apr. 13)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.9 (1956: Apr. 27)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.10 (1956: May 11)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.11 (1956: May 25)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.12 (1956: June 8)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.13 (1956: June 22)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.14 (1956: July 6)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.15 (1956: July 20)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.16 (1956: Aug. 3)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.17 (1956: Aug. 17)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.18 (1956: Aug. 31)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.19 (1956: Sept. 14)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.20 (1956: Sept. 28)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.21 (1956: Oct. 12)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.22 (1956: Oct. 26)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.23 (1956: Nov. 9)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.24 (1956: Nov. 23)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.25 (1956: Dec. 7)
  - Item 26: West Coast Sailors, 1956; Publication (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.26 (1956: Dec. 21)
- West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.1 (1957: Jan. 4)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.2 (1957: Jan. 18)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.3 (1957: Feb. 1)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.4 (1957: Feb. 15)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.5 (1957: Mar. 1)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.6 (1957: Mar. 15)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.7 (1957: Mar. 29)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.8 (1957: Apr. 12)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.9 (1957: Apr. 26)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.12 (1957: June 7)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.13 (1957: June 21)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.14 (1957: July 5)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.15 (1957: July 19)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.16 (1957: Aug. 2)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.17 (1957: Aug. 16)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.18 (1957: Aug. 30)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.19 (1957: Sept. 13)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.20 (1957: Sept. 27)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.21 (1957: Oct. 11)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.23 (1957: Nov. 8)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.24 (1957: Nov. 22)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.25 (1957: Dec. 6)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1957; Publication (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.26 (1957: Dec. 20)
- West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1958: Jan. 3)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.2 (1958: Jan. 17)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.3 (1958: Jan. 31)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.4 (1958: Feb. 14)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.5 (1958: Feb. 28)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.7 (1958: Mar. 28)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.8 (1958: Apr. 11)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.9 (1958: Apr. 25)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.10 (1958: May 9)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.11 (1958: May 23)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.12 (1958: June 6)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.13 (1958: June 20)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.14 (1958: July 4)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.15 (1958: July 18)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.16 (1958: Aug. 1)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.17 (1958: Aug. 15)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1958; Publication (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.18 (1958: Aug. 29)
- West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.13 (1960: June 17)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.15 (1960: July 15)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.16 (1960: July 29)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.18 (1960: Aug. 26)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.19 (1960: Sept. 9)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.20 (1960: Sept. 23)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.21 (1960: Oct. 7)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.22 (1960: Oct. 21)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.23 (1960: Nov. 4)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.24 (1960: Nov. 18)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.25 (1960: Dec. 2)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.26 (1960: Dec. 16)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1960; Publication (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.23:no.27 (1960: Dec. 30)
- West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1961: Jan. 13)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (1961: Jan. 27)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.3 (1961: Feb. 10)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.4 (1961: Feb. 24)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.5 (1961: Mar. 10)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.6 (1961: Mar. 24)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.7 (1961: Apr. 7)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.8 (1961: Apr. 21)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.9 (1961: May 5)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.10 (1961: May 19)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.19 (1961: Sept. 22)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.22 (1961: Nov. 3)
- West Coast Sailors, 1961-1962 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1961; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.24:no.24 (1961: Dec. 1)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.3 (1962: Feb. 9)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.4 (1962: Feb. 23)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.6 (1962: Mar. 23)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.7 (1962: Apr. 6)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.8 (1962: Apr. 20)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.9 (1962: May 4)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.10 (1962: May 18)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.11 (1962: June 1)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.12 (1962: June 15)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.13 (1962: June 29)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.14 (1962: July 13)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.15 (1962: July 27)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.16 (1962: Aug. 10)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.17 (1962: Aug. 24)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.18 (1962: Sept. 7)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.19 (1962: Sept. 21)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.20 (1962: Oct. 5)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.21 (1962: Oct. 19)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.22 (1962: Nov. 2)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.23 (1962: Nov. 16)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.24 (1962: Nov. 30)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.25 (1962: Dec. 14)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1962; Publication (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.25:no.26 (1962: Dec. 28)
- West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.1 (1963: Jan. 11)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.2 (1963: Jan. 25)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.3 (1963: Feb. 8)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.4 (1963: Feb. 22)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.5 (1963: Mar. 8)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.6 (1963: Mar. 22)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.7 (1963: Apr. 5)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.8 (1963: Apr. 19)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.9 (1963: May 3)